Guide to The Women's Sports Foundation Records 1950-2019 (bulk, 1974-2018) MS 3199
New-York Historical Society
- Series IV. Departmental records, 1971-2018; 146 Linear feet in 146 record cartons
  - Subseries IV.D. Education records, 1983-2012; 24 Linear feet in 24 record cartons
    - Board of Trustees policy handbook, 1997 January (Offsite-box 126, Folder 18)
    - Exhibitor information [disassembled binder], 2002 (Offsite-box 127, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1988 (Offsite-box 127, Folder 2)
    - Former intern information, circa 1990 (Offsite-box 127, Folder 3)
    - NGWSD information requests, 1989 (Offsite-box 127, Folder 4)
    - NGWSD, 1989 (Offsite-box 127, Folder 5)
    - NGWSD scripts, 1989 (Offsite-box 127, Folder 6)
    - NGWSD PR, 1989 (Offsite-box 127, Folder 7)
    - NGWSD volleyball game, 1989 (Offsite-box 127, Folder 8)
    - NGWSD high school packet, 1989 (Offsite-box 127, Folder 9)
    - NGWSD poster, 1989 (Offsite-box 127, Folder 10)
    - Congressional res., 1989 (Offsite-box 127, Folder 11)
    - NGWSD media and resolutions, 1989 (Offsite-box 127, Folder 12)
    - State Flo Hyman awards, 1989 (Offsite-box 127, Folder 13)
    - NGWSD state contacts, 1989 (Offsite-box 127, Folder 14)
    - NGWSD press releases, 1989 (Offsite-box 127, Folder 15)
    - NGWSD recruitment letters, 1988 (Offsite-box 127, Folder 16)
    - Minorities in sports research, 1989 (Offsite-box 127, Folder 17)
    - Press conference arrangements, 1989 (Offsite-box 127, Folder 18)
    - New Agenda I, 1983 (Offsite-box 127, Folder 19)
    - New Agenda II, 1987 (Offsite-box 127, Folder 20)
    - New Agenda II abstracts, 1987 (Offsite-box 127, Folder 21)
    - Coaches awards, 1988 (Offsite-box 127, Folder 22)
    - Script [Minorities in Sports], 1989 August 15 (Offsite-box 127, Folder 23)
    - Minority Report releases, 1989 (Offsite-box 127, Folder 24)
    - Minority Report media placement, 1989 (Offsite-box 127, Folder 25)
    - New York City schools, 1988 March (Offsite-box 127, Folder 26)
    - New York City school program, 1988 (Offsite-box 127, Folder 27)
    - Challenge of the Champions - scripts, releases, 1988 (Offsite-box 127, Folder 28)
    - Family Circle FSI, 1988 (Offsite-box 127, Folder 29)
    - Research (3 folders) (Offsite-box 127, Folder 30-32)
    - NGWSD state events (1 of 2 folders), 1989 (Offsite-box 127, Folder 33)
    - NGWSD state events (2 of 2 folders), 1989 (Offsite-box 128, Folder 1)
    - SFJD search, 1988 (Offsite-box 128, Folder 2)
    - SFJD search, 1989 (Offsite-box 128, Folder 3)
    - Risky business (2 folders), 2000-2001 (Offsite-box 128, Folder 4-5)
    - Health risks and the teen athlete study (4 folders), 2000-2001 (Offsite-box 128, Folder 6-9)
    - National committee on pay equity (2 folders), 2001 (Offsite-box 128, Folder 10-11)
    - Ethical relationships committee, 1993-1996 (Offsite-box 128, Folder 12)
    - Permission received - harassment packet, 1994 (Offsite-box 128, Folder 13)
    - Policies/ codes of ethics (Ethical relationships committee), 1994 (Offsite-box 128, Folder 14)
    - Academic network, 1992 (Offsite-box 128, Folder 15)
    - WSF research network potential projects, 1993 (Offsite-box 128, Folder 16)
    - Ad hoc committee on homophobia, 1994-1996 (Offsite-box 128, Folder 17)
    - Information on grants/ funding, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 128, Folder 18)
    - Letters- permission to reprint Title IX expert packet, 1996 (Offsite-box 128, Folder 19)
    - Bozell sponsorship, 1996 (Offsite-box 128, Folder 20)
    - Relevant articles - ethical relationships committee (2 folders), 1993-1996 (Offsite-box 129, Folder 1-2)
    - Gender testing, 1996-1997 (Offsite-box 129, Folder 3)
    - Gender verification, 1997 (Offsite-box 129, Folder 4)
    - Eating disorders (4 folders), 1991-1996 (Offsite-box 129, Folder 5-8)
    - Twenty challenges working copies and information, 1994 (Offsite-box 129, Folder 9)
    - National Committee on Pay Equity, 2000 (Offsite-box 129, Folder 10)
    - Scholarship guide playbook [disassembled binder], 1993 (Offsite-box 129, Folder 11)
    - Scholarship guide playbook [disassembled binder] (2 folders), 1995-1996 (Offsite-box 129, Folder 12-13)
    - NGWSD poster/ CAK/ certificate playbook [disassembled binder] (2 folders), 1995-1996 (Offsite-box 129, Folder 14-15)
    - Active Sisters proposal to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention for the National Physical Activity Program [disassembled binder] (3 folders), 1995 August 18 (Offsite-box 129, Folder 16-18)
    - The Balancing Act: A Woman's Guide to Sport & Fitness [disassembled binder], 1996 (Offsite-box 129, Folder 19)
    - Girls sports projects [disassembled binder] (2 folders), 1995-1996 (Offsite-box 130, Folder 1-2)
    - Coors guide - Work & Play: The Balancing Act II [disassembled binder] (2 folders), 1997 (Offsite-box 130, Folder 3-4)
    - North shore child & family guidance center [disassembled binder] (3 folders), 1999 (Offsite-box 130, Folder 5-7)
    - Coaches guide Spanish translation, 1990 (Offsite-box 130, Folder 8)
    - NGWSD t-shirts, 1996 (Offsite-box 130, Folder 9)
    - NGWSD resolution, 1995 (Offsite-box 130, Folder 10)
    - Host communication TAGG, 1996-1998 (Offsite-box 130, Folder 11)
    - [NGWSD], 1997 (Offsite-box 130, Folder 12)
    - NGWSD planning, 1998 (Offsite-box 130, Folder 13)
    - NGWSD planning, 1996 (Offsite-box 130, Folder 14)
    - Take a girl to a game day, 1997-1998 (Offsite-box 130, Folder 15)
    - Community action kit, 1997 (Offsite-box 130, Folder 16)
    - Budget, 1997 (Offsite-box 130, Folder 17)
    - NGWSD budget, 1996 (Offsite-box 130, Folder 18)
    - NGWSD poster, 1996 (Offsite-box 130, Folder 19)
    - NGWSD planning, 1997 (Offsite-box 130, Folder 20)
    - Education/ resource council meeting (1 of 3 folders), 2000 (Offsite-box 130, Folder 21)
    - Education/ resource council meeting (2 of 3 folders), 2000 (Offsite-box 131, Folder 1-2)
    - Athlete protection committee, 1996 (Offsite-box 131, Folder 3)
    - Council correspondence, 1999 (Offsite-box 131, Folder 4)
    - Expert/ resource council, 1997 (Offsite-box 131, Folder 5)
    - NCPE (National Center for Professional Education), 2002-2003 (Offsite-box 131, Folder 6)
    - Education/ resource council, 2001 (Offsite-box 131, Folder 7)
    - Pregnancy PR (2 folders), 1998 (Offsite-box 131, Folder 8-9)
    - Pregnancy - misc. (2 folders), 1996-1998 (Offsite-box 131, Folder 10-11)
    - Pregnancy - budget, 1997 (Offsite-box 131, Folder 12)
    - Pregnancy - funders, 1997 (Offsite-box 131, Folder 13)
    - NGWSD poster/ CAK/ certificate playbook [disassembled binder], 1996-1997 (Offsite-box 131, Folder 14)
    - Resource Council playbook [disassembled binder] (3 folders), 1995 (Offsite-box 131, Folder 15-17)
    - Sports in the lives of urban girls [disassembled binder], 1998 (Offsite-box 131, Folder 18)
    - Sport & Teen Pregnancy final report, 1998 June 15 (Offsite-box 131, Folder 19)
    - Sport & Teen Pregnancy final report, 1998 June 15 (Offsite-box 132, Folder 1)
    - RGK Foundation final report [disassembled binder], 2000 May 22 (Offsite-box 132, Folder 2)
    - RGK Foundation final report [disassembled binder], 2000 September 1 (Offsite-box 132, Folder 3)
    - Sporting chance, 1996-2000 (Offsite-box 132, Folder 4)
    - NYAD video follow up, 2002 (Offsite-box 132, Folder 5)
    - NYSIR/ WSF seminars, 2001-2002 (Offsite-box 132, Folder 6)
    - Teen pregnancy day, 2002 (Offsite-box 132, Folder 7)
    - Liberty game, 2003 (Offsite-box 132, Folder 8)
    - NCYS conference, 2003 November 6 (Offsite-box 132, Folder 9)
    - NCYS conference, 2002 October 26-29 (Offsite-box 132, Folder 10)
    - GAHPERD convention (Georgia Association for Health, Physical Education, Recreation and Dance), 2004 September 23-25 (Offsite-box 132, Folder 11)
    - White House project, 2001 (Offsite-box 132, Folder 12)
    - Homophobia project budget (2 folders), 2002 (Offsite-box 132, Folder 13-14)
    - Homophobia project (3 folders), 2004 (Offsite-box 132, Folder 15-17)
    - Homophobia - Lisa Thompson call (3 folders), 2003 (Offsite-box 132, Folder 18-20)
    - Homophobia project, 2003 (Offsite-box 132, Folder 21)
    - It takes a team: donations to project, 2003 (Offsite-box 132, Folder 22)
    - It takes a team: kit accounting, 2003 (Offsite-box 132, Folder 23)
    - It takes a team: budget info, 2002 (Offsite-box 132, Folder 24)
    - It takes a team: orders for video and kit, 2002 (Offsite-box 132, Folder 25)
    - It takes a team: new video and manual to-do's, 2004 (Offsite-box 132, Folder 26)
    - It takes a team: kit packaging, 2002 (Offsite-box 132, Folder 27)
    - It takes a team: VHS and DVD covers, 2004 (Offsite-box 132, Folder 28)
    - It takes a team: kit assembly, 2003 (Offsite-box 132, Folder 29)
    - It takes a team: revised manual and PDFs, 2004 (Offsite-box 132, Folder 30)
    - It takes a team: updates to manual list, 2004 (Offsite-box 132, Folder 31)
    - It takes a team: new re-produceable stickers LGBT athlete safe space, 2003 (Offsite-box 132, Folder 32)
    - It takes a team: stickers (revised), 2003 (Offsite-box 132, Folder 33)
    - It takes a team: DEANA, 2002 (Offsite-box 132, Folder 34)
    - It takes a team: closed captioning and streaming media questions, 2003 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 1)
    - It takes a team: banners, 2004 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 2)
    - It takes a team: website maintenance, 2004 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 3)
    - It takes a team: website updates, 2003-2004 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 4)
    - It takes a team: letterhead, 2002 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 5)
    - It takes a team: talking points cheat sheet, 2004 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 6)
    - It takes a team: press release, 2003 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 7)
    - It takes a team: kit production and review, 2002 October (Offsite-box 133, Folder 8)
    - It takes a team: stickers, 2002 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 9)
    - It takes a team: VSOC mini-kits, 2003 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 10)
    - It takes a team: Avery labels (NCLR stickers), 2003 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 11)
    - It takes a team: order forms, 2002 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 12)
    - It takes a team: itemized costs for revised mini kits, 2004 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 13)
    - It takes a team: feedback forms, circa 2002-2004 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 14)
    - It takes a team: video copies dub house job, 2002 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 15)
    - It takes a team: Dan Nocera, 2003 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 16)
    - It takes a team: correspondence with Dan Nocera re: post production video issues, 2003 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 17)
    - It takes a team: WSF MCC video meeting initial negotiations, 2002 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 18)
    - Pictogram project, 1995 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 19)
    - Teen pregnancy report (2 folders), 1998 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 20-21)
    - Pictogram project, 1995 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 22)
    - It takes a team: video (name and addresses) contact info, circa 2002 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 23)
    - It takes a team: video releases (confidential), 2002 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 24)
    - It takes a team: interview questions, 2002 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 25)
    - It takes a team: thank you to video contributors, 2003 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 26)
    - It takes a team: Jamie Bailey, 2003 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 27)
    - It takes a team: Dan Bozzuto, 2003 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 28)
    - It takes a team: Mike Crosby, 2002 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 29)
    - It takes a team: Andy Holder, 2003 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 30)
    - It takes a team: Lauren Perotti, 2002 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 31)
    - It takes a team: David McIlvride, Nicole LaViolet, Aiken Scherberger, 2002 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 32)
    - It takes a team: David McIlvride, 2002 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 33)
    - It takes a team: Dee Mosbacher, 2002 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 34)
    - It takes a team: Sue Mullaney, 2002 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 35)
    - It takes a team: Loren Ruffin, 2002 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 36)
    - It takes a team: Judy and Bob Miller, 2002 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 37)
    - It takes a team: Christopher Bergland, 2002 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 38)
    - It takes a team: Derik Peterson, 2002 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 39)
    - It takes a team: Ryan Quinn, 2002-2003 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 40)
    - It takes a team: Santiago, 2002 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 41)
    - It takes a team: Dwight Slater, 2003 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 42)
    - It takes a team: Esera Tvaolo, 2002 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 43)
    - It takes a team: Aaron Vays, 2002 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 44)
    - It takes a team: WSF - narration requests, 2002 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 45)
    - It takes a team: ABC news and sports (clips), 2003 (Offsite-box 133, Folder 46)
    - It takes a team: broadcast rights, 2002 (Offsite-box 134, Folder 1)
    - It takes a team: ESPN (clips), 2002 (Offsite-box 134, Folder 2)
    - Video clearances, 2000-2002 (Offsite-box 134, Folder 3)
    - US Open credentialing info, 2002 (Offsite-box 134, Folder 4)
    - [US Open] directions, map, contact info, 2002 (Offsite-box 134, Folder 5)
    - Rough cut video meeting, 2002 (Offsite-box 134, Folder 6)
    - New video script and clips, 2002 (Offsite-box 134, Folder 7)
    - New video credits, 2002 (Offsite-box 134, Folder 8)
    - New script, 2002 (Offsite-box 134, Folder 9)
    - Scripts, 2002 (Offsite-box 134, Folder 10)
    - Writing committee, 2002 (Offsite-box 134, Folder 11)
    - Writing committee meeting, 2002 August 12 (Offsite-box 134, Folder 12)
    - June writing group meeting agenda, 2002 (Offsite-box 134, Folder 13)
    - Drafts from writing committee, 2002 (Offsite-box 134, Folder 14)
    - NGWSD poster, 2001 (Offsite-box 134, Folder 15)
    - Coors (3 folders), 1998-1999 (Offsite-box 134, Folder 16-18)
    - Internet/ AOL, 1997 (Offsite-box 134, Folder 19)
    - Coaches guide info, 1998 (Offsite-box 134, Folder 20)
    - AAASP conference (American Association of Adapted Sports Programs), circa 1997-2000 (Offsite-box 134, Folder 21)
    - Scholarship guide, 1995-2000 (Offsite-box 134, Folder 22)
    - Encyclopedia project, 1997-2001 (Offsite-box 134, Folder 23)
    - Moving comfort clothing grants, circa 1997-2000 (Offsite-box 134, Folder 24)
    - SGMA grant, 1993 (Offsite-box 134, Folder 25)
    - Injury database project, 1997 (Offsite-box 134, Folder 26)
    - Girls sports, 1997-1998 (Offsite-box 134, Folder 27)
    - Nutrition brochure, 1998-1999 (Offsite-box 134, Folder 28)
    - Girl scouts (3 folders), 1994 (Offsite-box 134, Folder 29-31)
    - Mervyn's (3 folders), 1997-2000 (Offsite-box 135, Folder 1-3)
    - Health south, 1998 (Offsite-box 135, Folder 4)
    - Lycra (2 folders), 1999-2000 (Offsite-box 135, Folder 5-6)
    - Lycra guide, 1999 (Offsite-box 135, Folder 7)
    - Yes she can video (2 folders), 2000 (Offsite-box 135, Folder 8-9)
    - Skin cancer coalition, 1999 (Offsite-box 135, Folder 10)
    - Healthy mothers, healthy babies coalition, 1998 (Offsite-box 135, Folder 11)
    - IASMHF conference (International Association of Sports Museums and Halls of Fame), 1999 (Offsite-box 135, Folder 12)
    - BJK project - PR/ promotion year two, 2002 (Offsite-box 135, Folder 13)
    - BJK project site visits year one, 2001-2002 (Offsite-box 135, Folder 14)
    - BJK project year two - coaches guide, 2002 (Offsite-box 135, Folder 15)
    - BJK project year two - Guide to Life athletes/ educational material (2 folders), 2002 (Offsite-box 135, Folder 16-17)
    - BJK project year two - playbook, coaches guide background, 2002 (Offsite-box 135, Folder 18)
    - BJK project year two - journal, 2002 (Offsite-box 135, Folder 19)
    - BJK project year two - timeline, 2002 (Offsite-box 135, Folder 20)
    - BJK project year two - materials sent to D.G., 2002 (Offsite-box 135, Folder 21)
    - BJK project year two - illustrations, 2002 (Offsite-box 135, Folder 22)
    - BJK project year two - miscellaneous, 2002 (Offsite-box 136, Folder 1)
    - BJK project year one - evaluation, 2001 (Offsite-box 136, Folder 2)
    - BJK project - miscellaneous printed material, 2001-2002 (Offsite-box 136, Folder 3)
    - BJK project year 2 - fulfillment, 2002 (Offsite-box 136, Folder 4)
    - BJK project year two - peer leader guide, 2002 (Offsite-box 136, Folder 5)
    - BJK project - expert panel, 2002 (Offsite-box 136, Folder 6)
    - BJK project - correspondence, minutes, 2002 (Offsite-box 136, Folder 7)
    - BJK project - other print materials, 2001 (Offsite-box 136, Folder 8)
    - BJK project - budget/ timeline, 2001 (Offsite-box 136, Folder 9)
    - BJK project - Phillip Morris, 2001 (Offsite-box 136, Folder 10)
    - BJK project - cartoons, 2001 (Offsite-box 136, Folder 11)
    - BJK project - correspondence/ minutes, 2001 (Offsite-box 136, Folder 12)
    - BJK project - miscellaneous, 2001 (Offsite-box 136, Folder 13)
    - BJK project - athlete stories, 2001 (Offsite-box 136, Folder 14)
    - BJK project - PR/ promotion and distribution, 2001 (Offsite-box 136, Folder 15)
    - GoGirls registration/ logo, 2001 (Offsite-box 136, Folder 16)
    - BJK project - playbook (2 folders), 2001 (Offsite-box 136, Folder 17-18)
    - BJK project - expert panel review, 2001 (Offsite-box 136, Folder 19)
    - GoGirlGo [disassembled binder], 2002-2003 (Offsite-box 136, Folder 20)
    - GoGirlGo kits year three (2 of 7 folders), 2002-2003 (Offsite-box 136, Folder 21-22)
    - GoGirlGo kits year three (5 of 7 folders), 2002-2003 (Offsite-box 137, Folder 1-5)
    - GoGirlGo year four - National GoGirl character development, 2004 (Offsite-box 137, Folder 6)
    - GoGirlGo year four - National education kit, 2004 (Offsite-box 137, Folder 7)
    - GoGirlGo year four - National education program promotion, 2004 (Offsite-box 137, Folder 8)
    - GoGirlGo year four - National ambassador program, 2004 (Offsite-box 137, Folder 9)
    - GoGirlGo year four - National resources education, 2004 (Offsite-box 137, Folder 10)
    - GoGirlGo year four - National resources activism (3 folders), 2004 (Offsite-box 137, Folder 11-13)
    - GoGirlGo year five - National planning/ meeting/ agendas, 2005 (Offsite-box 137, Folder 14)
    - GoGirlGo year five - National resources educational kit, 2005 (Offsite-box 137, Folder 15)
    - GoGirlGo year five - educational materials scrapbook, 2005 (Offsite-box 137, Folder 16)
    - GoGirlGo year five - budget National education program, 2005 (Offsite-box 137, Folder 17)
    - GoGirlGo year five - educational materials, 2005 (Offsite-box 137, Folder 18)
    - GoGirlGo PepsiCo foundation proposal, 2004 (Offsite-box 137, Folder 19)
    - GoGirlGo funders, 2003 (Offsite-box 137, Folder 20)
    - Government funding guidelines, 2005 (Offsite-box 137, Folder 21)
    - GoGirlGo community New Hampshire, 2005 (Offsite-box 137, Folder 22)
    - GoGirlGo Buffalo, 2005 (Offsite-box 137, Folder 23)
    - GoGirlGo pilot communities San Jose, 2005 (Offsite-box 137, Folder 24)
    - GoGirlGo pilot communities Kansas City, 2005 (Offsite-box 137, Folder 25)
    - SASF contract, 2006 (Offsite-box 137, Folder 26)
    - San Antonio benchmark study, 2006 (Offsite-box 137, Folder 27)
    - San Antonio benchmark study, 2008 (Offsite-box 137, Folder 28)
    - GoGirlGo pilot communities, 2006 (Offsite-box 138, Folder 1)
    - Massachusetts GoGirlGo resources, 2004 (Offsite-box 138, Folder 2)
    - Nevada GoGirlGo resources, 2004 (Offsite-box 138, Folder 3)
    - GoGirlGo year six - National educational materials, 2007 (Offsite-box 138, Folder 4)
    - GoGirlGo year six - National planning, 2007 (Offsite-box 138, Folder 5)
    - GoGirlGo translations, 2006 (Offsite-box 138, Folder 6)
    - GoGirlGo in Cleveland, 2006 (Offsite-box 138, Folder 7)
    - GoGirlGo Chicago funders, 2006 (Offsite-box 138, Folder 8)
    - GoGirlGo year five - Chicago, 2004 (Offsite-box 138, Folder 9)
    - GoGirlGo year four - Chicago leadership summit, 2005 (Offsite-box 138, Folder 10)
    - GoGirlGo Chicago leadership summit, 2005 (Offsite-box 138, Folder 11)
    - GoGirlGo curriculum training, 2005 (Offsite-box 138, Folder 12)
    - GoGirlGo year one - Chicago research, 2002 (Offsite-box 138, Folder 13)
    - GoGirlGo Chicago Hispanic initiative (2 folders), 2005-2006 (Offsite-box 138, Folder 14-15)
    - GoGirlGo year two - final report, 2003 (Offsite-box 138, Folder 16)
    - BJK project evaluation year two, 2003 (Offsite-box 138, Folder 17)
    - BJK project year two - trademark, 2002 (Offsite-box 138, Folder 18)
    - GoGirlGo year three - evaluation, 2004 (Offsite-box 138, Folder 19)
    - GoGirlGo year three - final report, 2003-2004 (Offsite-box 138, Folder 20)
    - BJK project budget, 2002 (Offsite-box 138, Folder 21)
    - BJK project, 2003 (Offsite-box 138, Folder 22)
    - GoGirlGo year three - budget, 2003-2004 (Offsite-box 138, Folder 23)
    - GoGirlGo year three, 2003 (Offsite-box 138, Folder 24)
    - GoGirlGo year four - white paper, 2004 (Offsite-box 138, Folder 25)
    - GoGirlGo research facts white paper, 2004 (Offsite-box 138, Folder 26)
    - GoGirlGo year four - National report card, 2004-2005 (Offsite-box 139, Folder 1)
    - GoGirlGo research team meeting, 2005 (Offsite-box 139, Folder 2)
    - GoGirlGo year four - communities planning, 2004 (Offsite-box 139, Folder 3)
    - GoGirlGo potential communities, 2004 (Offsite-box 139, Folder 4)
    - GoGirlGo year four - National proposals/ fundraising, 2004 (Offsite-box 139, Folder 5)
    - GoGirlGo year four - community resources, 2003-2004 (Offsite-box 139, Folder 6)
    - GoGirlGo year four - National activism campaign, 2004 (Offsite-box 139, Folder 7)
    - GoGirlGo year four - National budget activism campaign, 2004 (Offsite-box 139, Folder 8)
    - GoGirlGo year four - National fundraising events, 2004 (Offsite-box 139, Folder 9)
    - GoGirlGo year four - National GoGirlGo.com, 2004 (Offsite-box 139, Folder 10)
    - GoGirlGo year four - National strategic plan, 2004 (Offsite-box 139, Folder 11)
    - GoGirlGo year four - National PR, 2004 (Offsite-box 139, Folder 12)
    - GoGirlGo year four - National planning/ minutes/ agendas, 2004 (Offsite-box 139, Folder 13)
    - GoGirlGo year four - National budget education program, 2004 (Offsite-box 139, Folder 14)
    - GoGirlGo year four - National education program evaluation, 2004 (Offsite-box 139, Folder 15)
    - GoGirlGo annual kits (5 folders), 2002-2006 (Offsite-box 139, Folder 16-20)
    - GoGirlGo guides and stickers (2 folders), circa 2004-2006 (Offsite-box 139, Folder 21-22)
    - BJK project GoGirlGo year one interim report [disassembled binder], 2002 March 8 (Offsite-box 139, Folder 23)
    - BJK project GoGirlGo year two interim report [disassembled binder] (2 folders), 2003 January 23 (Offsite-box 140, Folder 1-2)
    - BJK project GoGirlGo year one and two final reports [disassembled binder], 2002-2003 (Offsite-box 140, Folder 3)
    - BJK project GoGirlGo year three interim report [disassembled binder], 2003 October 14 (Offsite-box 140, Folder 4)
    - BJK project GoGirlGo year three final report [disassembled binder] (2 folders), 2004 March 5 (Offsite-box 140, Folder 5-6)
    - BJK project GoGirlGo year four final report [disassembled binder] (2 folders), 2004 March 7 (Offsite-box 140, Folder 7-8)
    - GoGirlGo Philip Morris USA youth smoking prevention interim report, 2004 August 2 (Offsite-box 140, Folder 9)
    - GoGirlGo Chicago Hispanic Girls Initiative final report [disassembled binder], 2006 August 15 (Offsite-box 140, Folder 10)
    - BJK project GoGirlGo final report [disassembled binder], 2006 October 10 (Offsite-box 140, Folder 11)
    - GoGirlGo San Antonio launch [disassembled binder], 2006 November 1 (Offsite-box 140, Folder 12)
    - GoGirlGo Philip Morris USA youth smoking prevention interim report, 2007 January 31 (Offsite-box 140, Folder 13)
    - Girl serving organizations: Atlanta Women's Alliance, 2004 (Offsite-box 140, Folder 14)